The Louds are about to rule.
The Loud House Movie is a animation, family,
comedy film directed by Dave Needham.
The Loud family travel to Scotland and discover they are descendants of
Scottish royalty as they move into their giant ancestral castle.
Lincoln / The Duke (voice), played by Asher Bishop.
Angus (voice), played by David Tennant.
Morag (voice), played by Michelle Gomez.
Mom / 1600's Mom (voice), played by Jill Talley.
Dad / 1600's Dad (voice), played by Brian Stepanek.
Lori (voice), played by Catherine Taber.
The Loud House Movie is a 2021 American animated musical fantasy comedy
film based on the Nickelodeon series The Loud House.
Produced by Nickelodeon Movies, it was directed by Dave Needham in his directorial debut, from a screenplay by Kevin Sullivan and Chris Viscardi, and starring the voices of David Tennant, Michelle Gomez, Katy Townsend, and the regular voice cast of the
series; consisting of Asher Bishop, Jill Talley, Brian Stepanek, Catherine Taber, Liliana Mumy, Nika Futterman, Cristina Pucelli, Jessica DiCicco, Grey Griffin, Lara Jill Miller, and Andre Robinson, who reprise their respective roles.
The first film in the franchise, set between the fourth and fifth seasons of The Loud House, it tells the story of the Louds going to
Scotland, where they learn that they are descendants from royalty and own a castle, while contending with an evil plot.
Originally slated for a 2020 theatrical release by Paramount Pictures, it
instead had a digital release on Netflix on August 20, 2021.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted.